wicproject.com 2013-05-22

# Disclosure & Privacy Policies - The WiC Project - Faith. Free Giveaways. Product Reviews. Recipes.

## Disclosure Policy

This policy is valid from 06 October 2009

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation. The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made in this blog.

The owner(s) of this blog is not compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. However, we may receive complimentary samples of the product from the manufacturer or the representing PR agency to write our review. This will not bias our reviews, which will always be our honest opinions. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the blog owners. If we claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic or product or service area, we will only endorse products or services that we believe, based on our expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. The author(s) of this blog are not medical professionals, and you should never substitute information from this Blog for information obtained from a licensed medical professional; always consult your doctor before using any prescription, drugs, supplements, or undergoing any treatments. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

We may include affiliate links in our posts. We may receive monetary compensation if you purchase through an affiliate link.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org

## Facebook Relationship

In order to comply with [the latest Facebook Promotion Guidelines](http://www.facebook.com/promotions_guidelines.php) (revised 5/11/11), the following statements are true:

  * Giveaway participants release Facebook from any responsibility whatsoever.
  * Giveaways on this blog are in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with, Facebook.
  * Giveaway participants are providing information to this blog and giveaway sponsors only; not to Facebook.

## Privacy Policy

**Creative Patience, LLC respects your privacy.**

 ****This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.wicproject.com and how it is used.

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Creative Patience, LLC, except in the case of giveaway winners who will be receiving their prize shipment directly from the vendor. In this case, Creative Patience, LLC will notify the winner requesting the information for this purpose. If you do not wish to provide this information, you will forfeit your prize.

**Credit card details**

Creative Patience, LLC will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Creative Patience, LLC.

**External Sites.**

Creative Patience, LLC is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Creative Patience, LLC to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Creative Patience, LLC does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Creative Patience, LLC and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Creative Patience, LLC have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.wicproject.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.wicproject.com does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.wicproject.com.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.wicproject.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

Google Adsense

Amazon Associates

Commission Junction

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.wicproject.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.wicproject.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.wicproject.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@wicproject.com.
